this summer
between honor and dishonor between
family and enemies between July and
August a line will be drawn and then
colored in yellow jump jump
rest rest I know we've had a rough day
I'm sure we can put all that behind us
on July 27th a secret will be revealed
like a dad you can see the four states
that border Springfield oh wow never had
a man in Kentucky oh yeah an empire mean
wise we have two buttons behind this
desk wooden will supply your town with
power the other releases the hounds just
look into your heart and you will find
the answer apology is tossed around a
lot these days job 20th Century Fox
presents Homer horribly Marge
Lisa bar
magic mr. Birds Smithers Krusty Barney
Lenny Carl itchy boom what grandpa opera
wig of Milhouse rail Selma bumblebee
mili Jimbo Reverend Lovejoy here's the
money shot and a cast of thousands in
the movie event 18 years in the making
planners always room for one more in the
Flanders clan and the fate of the world
hangs in the balance
something funny
The Simpsons movie in theaters worldwide
July 27th